freebies4mom.com 2017-09-11

# Privacy Policy

_This Privacy Policy for Freebies4Mom.com, a personal blog, was last updated on  March 19, 2015.  
_

This blog, _Freebies 4 Mom_ , is a personal blog written and edited by Heather Hernandez of Freebies 4 Mom, LLC and found at http://Freebies4Mom.com. For questions about this blog, please [**contact Heather**](https://freebies4mom.com/contact/).

**Privacy Policy**

Your privacy is important to me and I will respect the information that you submit to me in order to subscribe to my blog, enter giveaways, participate in a poll or survey, or post a comment.  This blog does not collect information from minors, only from adults ages 18 and above.  I will never give or sell your email address to anyone.  This blog is hosted by WordPress, and if you have any questions about the privacy of information you submit through this blog you should read [**WordPress’ Privacy Policy**](http://wordpress.org/about/privacy/).  This blog uses Google Docs forms to securely collect giveaway entries.  I do not give the information you submit through Google Docs to giveaway sponsors or anyone else except to announce the winner.  If you win I will post your first name and initial of your last name, but I will not share your email address.  Your email address and full name are always kept private and not shared with anyone unless I have your permission.  If you have any questions about the privacy of information you submit through Google you should read[ **Google’s Privacy Policy**](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ "Google").

In general, you are responsible for the information you submit when you subscribe to my blog, enter giveaways, participate in a poll or survey, or post a comment.  Your comments on posts and profile information can be read by anyone and I discourage you from including your email address or other personally identifying information.  I do allow you to post comments as “Anonymous” as a way to help protect your privacy.

Cookies are collected by third party vendors, including Google, to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to _Freebies 4 Mom_. Google’s use of the [**DoubleClick DART cookie**](http://www.google.com/intl/en/privacy/ "Google Privacy Policy") enables it and its partners to serve ads to the users of _Freebies 4 Mom_ based on their visit to _Freebies 4 Mom_ and/or other sites on the internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [**advertising opt-out page**](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html "http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html"). Users may also opt out of the use of some cookies, but not all, at the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out website at [**www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt-out.asp**](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp "http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp"). **  
**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see:  **[http://www.networkadvertising. org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)**

Please **[contact Heather Hernandez](https://freebies4mom.com/contact/) **if you have any questions about this Privacy Policy. You may also be interested in reading my [**Disclosure Policy**](http://wp.me/p1vcSC-7Z9 "Disclosure Policy") and my [**Disclaimer Policy**](http://wp.me/p1vcSC-7Z8 "Disclaimer Policy").
